<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Engineering on Hugo Quickstart with Pico CSS</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/data-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Engineering on Hugo Quickstart with Pico CSS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 13:32:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/data-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcoming the Future</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 13:32:25 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi there! My name is Angel. Join me as I embark on this blogging journey, where I&amp;rsquo;ll share my experiences, insights, and enthusiasm for data engineering, analytics, and artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-am-i&#34;&gt;Who Am I?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a Data and Analytics Engineer by trade, who has also architected data solutions at an enterprise scale. My journey began at GameFly as a Business Analyst Intern, where I was later hired full-time after completing my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science from CSU Fullerton.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-interests&#34;&gt;My Interests&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My interests revolve around using technology to solve complex problems. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s building fault-tolerant data pipelines, designing scalable analytics platforms, or experimenting with machine learning, I&amp;rsquo;m all in. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly fascinated by the potential of AI to transform industries, enhance human capabilities, and create a more interconnected world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, my curiosity isn&amp;rsquo;t limited to software development. I&amp;rsquo;m a voracious consumer of stand-up comedy, avid follower of the latest in physics and space exploration, and enjoy experimenting with different flavors in baking and cooking. Oh and I played the clarinet from 8th-12th grade. (Bass clarinet and contra bass clarinet too!) The bass and contra-bass were for concert hall performances. If you have never seen a bass or contra-bass before, a bass clarinet looks like a clarinet was shot with the opposite of a shrink ray, an anti-shrink ray if you will. A contra-bass has two variations, version 1 looks it was hit but that anti-shrink ray, and version 2 looks like a radioactive paperclip bit a bass clarinet then hit with an anti-shrink ray again. All this to say that this is where my appreciation for music stems from. However, my love for a groovy funky bass line will always make me smile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS I have been known to play video game on NES, N64, GameBoy, DS, Wii, Switch, XBOX, XBOX 360, XBONE, PS1/2/3/4, and PSP&amp;hellip; to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-blog&#34;&gt;Why blog?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog is more than a platform for sharing knowledge; it&amp;rsquo;s a space for connecting with like-minded individuals, sparking conversations, and fostering a community of tech enthusiasts and dreamers. Here, I will share insights from my professional experiences, general interests, and explore the intersection of technology with society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-connect&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Connect&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a fellow data professional, an AI enthusiast, or simply curious about the impact of technology on our world, I invite you to join me on this journey. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the possibilities and build a future where technology amplifies our potential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more posts, and feel free to reach out through my social media channels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
